- 안녕, 레이첼!
- 안녕
-Oh! Hey, Rach!
-Hi.
- 즐거운 발렌타인 데이 보내라!
- 너두!
-Happy Valentine's Day!
-You too!
로스네 집에서 사는 거 어때?
How's living at Ross'?
좋아, 하루종일 디스커버리 채널을
보게 만드는 것만 빼놓고
It's good, except he makes us watch
the Discovery Channel all day long.
중세 시대에 못 생긴 어떤 사람한테
정말 지루한 일이 일어났지
Something really boring happened
to someone ugly in the Middle Ages.
고마워요
나중에 보자
Oh, thank you.
I'll see you guys later.
저 커피는 참 좋겠다
That is one lucky
to-go cup of coffee.
이젠 감정을 정리하지 그래
너 이런 모습 보는거 싫어
I wish you would get over her.
I hate seeing you like this.
내가 도울 일 없겠니?
내 윗도리 속 보여줄까?
Is there anything I can do for you?
Do you wanna look down my top?
고맙다, 근데 나중에
Thanks. Maybe later.
- 건터, 스콘 좀 갖다 줄래요?
- 뭐 원하는 거 있어요?
-Gunther, can I get a scone?
-Want anything?
원하는 거 많아요
I want a lot of things.
내가 사랑하는 여자랑
발렌타인 데이에 같이 있고 싶고
I wanna be with the woman I love
on Valentine's Day.
그 여자도 나를
사랑해주길 바라고
I want her to love me back.
그럴 수 없다는 이 쓰라린 고통에서
벗어나고 싶어요
And I want relief from the wrenching
pain of knowing that won't happen!
빨간 베이글 있는데
We have red bagels.
좋아요
Okay.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'출산 비디오'
너희들 지금까지
같이 사는 건 괜찮아?
So how do you guys
like living together so far?
- 아, 좋아
- 그래
-Oh, it's been good.
-Yeah.
로스는 부스러기에 너보다
더 까다로운 것만 빼고
Except Ross is more uptight
about crumbs than you are.
소파 안에 닭다리가 들어 있더라
There was a drumstick in the couch.
난 부스러기에
까다로운 게 아니야
And I am not uptight about crumbs.
그건 있잖아
It's just that, you know..
부스러기가 있음 생쥐가 꼬이고
생쥐는 뭐 싸놓고 가고
crumbs attract mice.
And mice leave droppings.
그래서 대역병이 시작된 거야
And that's how the plague started.
그런 시대를 다시
겪고 싶다면야
So you wanna relive that again..
대역병은 생쥐들이
퍼뜨린 게 아냐
Mice didn't start the plague.
시궁쥐들이 퍼뜨렸지
Rats did.
정확히 말하자면
노르웨이 시궁쥐
Rattus norvegicus, to be exact.
어휴, 로스
Oh, good God, Ross.
가끔 만화도 좀 보게 해줘
Nick at Nite, once in a while.
나 가야겠다
안녕
All right, I'm going.
Bye.
피비, 잠깐 여기 있어봐
Phoebe, will you wait here?
- 네 의견 좀 물어볼 게 있거든
- 그래
-I wanna get your opinion on something.
-Yeah.
너랑 레이첼 같이 사는 것에
대해서 모나 반응은 어때?
How does Mona feel about
Rachel moving in?
이제 곧 말하려고
I'm on my way to tell her.
모나가 일주일 내내 없었거든
근데 괜찮을 거야
She's been away all week,
but she'll be cool.
이제까지 무척 협조적이었거든
She's been so supportive.
"화석은 내 친구"라고 써진
아기 티셔츠도 사줬어
She even got the baby a T-shirt
that says "Fossils are my friends."
모나, 아부 한 번 심하네
Come on, Mona. Don't kiss ass.
그럼 나 가야겠다
So I'm gonna take off.
이런! 레이첼이 이 테이프
보고 싶어 했는데
Oh, shoot! Oh, shoot!
Rachel wanted to see this tape.
- 뭔데?
- 내 친구 출산 비디오야
-What is it?
-My friend giving birth.
너희 아파트로 좀 갖고 갈래?
Could you take it to your apartment?
"캔디와 쿠키"?
"Candy and Cookie"?
캔디는 엄마고, 쿠키는 딸이야
Candy's the mom,
Cookie's the daughter.
아빠 이름도 쿠키야
The father's name is also Cookie.
난 왜 이런 사람들하고
친구인 거야?
Why am I friends with these people?
피비야, 이리와 봐
Phoebe, come here.
욕실에서 뭐 보여줄 게 있어
I wanna show you
something in the bathroom.
모니카, 철 좀 들어라
Monica, grow up.
- 네 뒤에 감춘 게 뭐야?
- 피비의 의견을 듣고 싶은 것들
-What's behind your back?
-Something I want Phoebe's opinion on.
- 내 의견은 싫어?
- 별로
-You don't want my opinion?
-Not really.
왜 이래, 난 네 오빠잖아
나한테 물어 봐
Come on, I'm your older brother.
Ask me.
그러죠, 오라버니
Okay, big brother.
어떤 걸 입어야 오라버니 친구께서
오빠 동생이랑 그걸 하고 싶어할까?
Which one would make your best friend
want to do your little sister?
빨간 거
The red one.
안녕
Hey.
요즘 네가 우울한 거 같아서
기분 풀어줄 누군가를 데리고 왔어
I know you're depressed,
so I brought someone to cheer you up.
바로 문 밖에, 진짜 살아있는
털 많은 놀이 친구가 있어
Right outside is a real,
live, furry playmate.
네 친구 제인이랑은
다시 안 잘 거야
I'm not sleeping
with your friend Jane again.
우와, 개잖아!
Hey, a dog!
제인이랑 많이 닮은 건
인정해라
Who, you gotta admit,
looks a lot like Jane.
세상에서 가장 행복한 개야
내 친구 웬디한테서 빌려왔지
He's the happiest dog ever.
I borrowed him from my friend Wendy.
얘가 네 기분 풀어줄 때까지
데리고 있어도 돼
So you can keep him
till he cheers you up.
나도 가끔 얘를 빌려 와
I borrow him myself
from time to time..
내가 우울해질 때마다
when I get depressed
thinking about..
세계의 기근과 빈곤에 대해
생각하느라고
world hunger, poverty..
그렇다고 너의 아픔이
사소한 것이라는 건 아냐
Not to trivialize your pain.
정말 고맙다, 피비
우리 재미있게 지내자
Thanks so much, Pheebs.
We are gonna have so much fun!
으으, 그런 뜻의 재미 말구
Oh, not that kind of fun.
해피 발렌타인 데이!
Happy Valentine's!
금방 나갈게, 덜 편하지만
더 야한 거 입는 중이야
I'm slipping into something a bit less
comfortable and a bit more slutty.
"캔디와 쿠키"?
"Candy and Cookie"?
"캔디와 쿠키"!
"Candy and Cookie"?!
모니카가 나한테 포르노를
빌려다 준 건가?
Monica got me porn?
여자들끼리 하는 포르노!
Girl-on-girl porn?!
우리 마누라가 날 정말 사랑하나 봐!
She really must love me!
- 자, 긴장 풀고
- 성 발렌타인님, 고맙수다
-Yeah, just relax.
-I love you, St. Valentine.
어어, 저거 좀 그런데
Whoa, whoa, that's not pretty.
자, 힘줘요!
Now push!
으악, 너무 아파요!
Oh, God, it hurts!
세상에, 이건 최악의 포르노다!
Worst porn ever!
- 어떻게 좀 멈춰 봐요!
- 지금 그러려고 해요!
-Oh, make it stop!
-I am trying!
가서 공 물어오는거다, 알았지?
가서 공 물어와!
Get the ball. Ready? Get the ball!
너 귀엽긴 한데 좀 멍청하다
You're cute, but you're not too smart.
근데 내가 이 공 던졌었나?
Did I just throw this?
- 안녕
-Hi.
이것들을 실수로 내 물건이랑
같이 싸버렸어
I accidentally packed these
with my stuff.
- 얘는 뭐야?
- 피비 친구 개
-Who is this?
-Phoebe's friend's dog.
진짜 이름을 몰라서
난 그냥 모짜렐라라고 불러
I don't know his real name.
I call him Mozzarella.
너 정말 귀엽구나, 너랑 놀고
싶은데 일하러 가야 돼
You are so cute. I wish I could play,
but I've gotta go to work.
회의 전에는 이렇게 얘기하는 걸
멈춰야 하는데, 정말로
I hope I stop talking like this
before my meeting. Yes, I do.
안녕, 조이
진짜 안 멈춰지네
Bye-bye, Joey.
Seriously, I can't stop it.
이리 와 봐! 야!
Come here! Hey!
레이첼이야, 여기서 살았었지
That's Rachel. She used to live here.
너한테 숨길 필요는 없겠지
저 여자를 사랑해
Might as well be honest with you.
We love her.
하지만 내 여자가 될 수는 없어
But we can't have her.
정말 그리워
I really miss her.
이해하지?
너도 수놈이잖아
Hey, you understand, right?
You're a guy.
수놈이었었군
Well, you used to be.
나 어때?
So, what do you think?
아직 쓸만하지
I've still got it.
- 이거 왜 빌려다 준 거야?
- 이게 뭔데?
-Why did you get me this?
-What is it?
소리 지르고, 피나고
거기가 벌어지는 거
It's yelling, bleeding, dilating.
으악, 거기가 벌어져!
Oh, the dilating!
이거 출산 비디오잖아?
피비껀데, 자기 이거 왜 봤어?
Is this the video of the birth? It's
Phoebe's. Why were you watching it?
발렌타인 데이라고 자기가
포르노 빌려다 준 줄 알았지
I thought maybe you got me porn
for Valentine's Day.
발렌타인 데이라고 내가 포르노를
빌려다 줄 거라 생각했다면
If you thought I was gonna
get you porn for Valentine's Day..
맞았어
you were right.
스타가 되고 싶어 도시로 온
한 여자 얘기인데
It's about a girl who moves
to the city in search of stardom..
결국엔 많은 남자들과
섹스 하는 걸로 끝나
but ends up having sex
with a lot of guys.
이거 별 네 개짜리인데
It got four stars.
가만, 이거 별이 아니네
Wait a minute. Those aren't stars.
- 어쨌든, 봐 볼래?
- 그게...
-Anyway, you wanna take a look?
-Well..
- 별로 그런 기분이 안 나는걸
- 자기, 왜 그래?
-I'm not really in a sexy mood.
-Hey, what's going on?
자기 죠스 처음 보고 나서
Remember the first time
you saw Jaws..
물에 다시 들어 가기까지
얼마나 오래 걸렸는지 기억 나?
how long it took
to go back in the water?
자기야, 이까지 테이프으로
발렌타인 데이를 망칠 수는 없잖아
We can't let this tape
wreck Valentine's Day.
극복해야 해
You gotta get past it.
말에서 떨어지면 다시
말에 올라타는 거야
Just get back on the horse.
안 그러면 그 말이 방에 가서
추리닝으로 갈아 입는다
Otherwise, the horse is gonna go into the
bedroom and change into her sweatpants.
- 자기가 이거 안 봐서 그래
- 출산은 자연스럽고 아름다운 거야
-Okay, you don't know. You didn't see it.
-Childbirth is beautiful.
아름다워? 그래?
Oh, beautiful? Really?
이게 아름답다고?
You think this is beautiful?
으악! 엄마가 날 미워하는 것도
다 이유가 있었어!
Oh, my God!
No wonder my mother hates me!
- 봤지, 자기야, 저거...
- 건들지 마!
-See, honey, there's..
-Don't touch me!
- 안녕!
-Hi!
-Hey!
- 아틀란틱 시티 어땠어?
- 좋았지
-How was Atlantic City?
-Good.
자기 주려고 선물 가져왔어
I brought you back a present.
뭐하러...
You didn't have to..
Saltwater taffy?!
소금물 태피네!
고마워
Thanks.
흥미로운 건, 사실 이건 바닷물로
만드는 게 아니라
Interestingly, it isn't made
with seawater.
맹물에 소금 타서 만든 거야
It's actually made
with salted fresh water.
재미 없지
That's not interesting.
- 재밌는데
- 그렇지, 자기 정말 보고 싶었어!
-I think it's interesting.
-Me too. I missed you!
나두
Me too.
- 지난 한 주는 어땠어?
- 괜찮았어
-How was your week?
-Good.
- 아기가 발로 차기 시작했어
- 우와, 정말!
-The baby started kicking.
-How exciting!
놀라웠어, 슬픈 건 아기가 처음
찼을 때 내가 없었다는 거야
It was amazing. The only thing is,
I wasn't there the first time.
- 저런
- 이런 걸 다 놓치고 있어서
-Oh, no.
-I was missing out on all this stuff.
- 조이가 레이첼보고 나랑 살라고 했어
- 웃겼어
-Joey suggested Rachel move in with me.
-Yeah, right.
- 뭐가?
- 조이는 농담을 해두
-What?
-Joey cracks me up.
"전처한테 들어와 살라고 해
이상할 거 없잖아"
"Have your ex-wife move in.
That wouldn't be awkward."
상상해 봐, 내가 며칠 없는 동안
Imagine, I go away for a few days..
내 남자 친구가 자기가 임신시킨
여자랑 살고 있다고 말야
and my boyfriend is living
with a woman he got pregnant.
그래서 조이한테 뭐라고 했어?
So, what'd you tell him?
레이첼이랑 같이 산다고
모나한테 얘기 안 했어?
You didn't tell Mona
Rachel moved in?
모나는 완전히 미친 생각이라고
여기는 것 같아서
She seemed to think
it was such a crazy idea.
게다가 태피까지 줬는데
Plus, she got me taffy.
- 정말? 나 그거 못 먹어봤는데
- 한 번도?
-Really? I've never had any.
-Ever?
우리 엄마는 자살 계획하느라
소금물 캔디엔 관심 없었다고나 할까
My mom was too busy planning her
suicide to provide saltwater treats.
고마워
Thank you.
모나한테 말하기는 할 거야?
Are you gonna tell her?
해야지, 우선 좀 알랑거리고
I will. I want to butter her up first.
저녁 식사에 데리고 가서 아주
로맨틱한 분위기를 만들고
I'm gonna take her to dinner,
do all this romantic stuff.
내가 최고의 남자 친구라고
생각하게 만든 다음
When she thinks
I'm the best boyfriend ever..
임신한 전처가 나랑
살고 있다고 얘기하는 거야
I'll tell her my pregnant
ex-girlfriend is living with me.
이런 말 했나 모르겠는데
모나는 참 운도 좋다
If I haven't said it before,
she's a lucky, lucky lady.
그래서 어디에...?
뭐 이딴 게 다 있어?
So where are..?
What the crap is up with this stuff?
이게 껌이야, 음식이야?
도대체 뭐야?
Is it gum? Is it food?
What's the deal?
어, 괜찮은데
핑크 색 먹어봐도 돼?
Oh, it's nice.
May I try a pink one?
그래서 아주 완벽한
계획을 짜야 해
So I just have to plan
the perfect night.
넌 지금껏
최고의 데이트가 뭐야?
Hey, what's the best date
you ever had?
작년에 그렉 헤이맨이
정말 괜찮은 초밥 저녁을 사줬어
Last year, Greg Hayman took me
to a very nice sushi dinner.
그리고 근처 연구소까지
낭만적인 산책을 했고
Then we took a romantic walk
to a nearby research lab..
연구소를 부수고 원숭이
20마리를 풀어줬어
where we trashed the place
and freed 20 monkeys.
그럴 줄 알았어!
내가 미친 게 아니었다구!
I knew it!
I knew I wasn't crazy!
작년에 버스 정류장에서
원숭이가 나한테 덤볐단 말야!
Last year, a monkey
did attack me at the bus stop!
나랑 레이첼은 친구고
레이첼은 로스랑 과거가 있고...
So between her and me being friends,
and her history with Ross..
그러니 레이첼과는
이루어질 수 없을 거야
it just isn't gonna happen.
네 놈이 고양이를
사랑하는 거나 마찬가지야
It'd be like you falling in love
with a cat.
- 안녕
- 왔냐
-Hey.
우리 예쁜 개 잘 지내나?
내가 젤 예뻐 하는 개 잘 있었어?
How's my favorite dog, huh?
How's my favorite dog?
풀이 죽어있네
You're subdued.
- 맥주 먹였어?
- 아니
-Did you give him a beer?
-No.
- 잠깐만, 얘기 좀 하자
- 그래
-Will you excuse us? We need to talk.
-Sure.
어, 나 말이야?
Oh, me, right.
- 왜 저렇게 침울해 보여? 무슨 일이야?
- 아무 것도
-He's miserable. What happened to him?
-Nothing.
- 얘기만 했을 뿐이야
- 무슨 얘기?
-We talked about stuff.
-What stuff?
레이첼 얘기
Rachel stuff.
개가 너 때문에 우울해졌어!
세상에서 제일 행복한 개인데
Oh, Joey, you bummed him out!
This is the happiest dog in the world.
너랑 딱 하루 있었는데
좀 보라구!
He spends a day with you, and look!
숨은 쉬잖아
He's breathing.
개가 보고 있으니까
즐거운 척 해, 알았지?
Okay, well, he's watching us
so just look happy, okay?
- 웬디한테 다시 갖다 줘야겠어
- 개 괜찮아
-I'll take him to Wendy's.
-He's fine.
잘 봐
Look.
여기 공 있다!
Here's your ball!
가서 물어와!
Get your ball!
가서...
Get..
아, 알았다
Of course.
테니스 공은 싫겠지
You don't want a tennis ball.
미트볼이 있는데 말야
Not when you can have a meatball.
자, 미트볼 물어와
Come on, get the meatball.
세상에, 내가
무슨 짓을 한 거야?
God, what have I done to you?
내가 개를 망가뜨렸어, 피비!
개를 망가뜨렸어!
I broke the dog, Pheebs!
I broke the dog!
고마워
Thanks.
나 모나 데리러 갈 건데
넌 오늘 밤 뭐 할 거니?
I'm going to pick up Mona.
What are you doing tonight?
어, 굉장한 발렌타인 데이
계획이 있지
Oh, I got big Valentine's plans.
중국음식 배달이 오는 중이고
네 소금물 태피도 있구
I got my Chinese food on the way,
and your saltwater taffy.
재밌는 건 말야
이건 바닷물로 만든 게 아니라...
Interestingly, it isn't made
with seawater..
우리 그 다큐멘터리 같이 봤잖아
We actually watched
the documentary together.
아, 중국 음식 왔다
돈 가져 와야지
Oh, my Chinese food.
I'll get my cash.
모나?
Mona?
어찌 된...
안녕, 자기야!
What are..?
Hi! How are you?
내가 데리러 가기로 했잖아
I'm supposed to pick you up.
내가 자기 주려고 발렌타인
저녁을 만들어 왔어, 놀랐지?
I made you a Valentine's dinner.
Surprise!
- 어, 안녕하세요!
- 안녕하세요
-Oh! Hey, Mona!
-Hi, Rachel.
레이첼이 여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
What's she doing here?
모르겠어
I have no idea.
나 TV 보고 있을게
필요하면 불러
I'll be watching TV
if anybody needs me.
정말로 저 여자 뭐 하는 거야?
What is she doing?
요즘 들어 우리집에
와 있는 걸 좋아해
Lately she just likes
hanging out here.
- 왜?
- 외로운가 보지
-Why?
-I think she's lonely.
하지만 오늘은 발렌타인 데이잖아
가라고 하면 안 돼?
But it's Valentine's Day.
Can't we ask her to go?
안 돼, 감정적으로 무지
예민해져 있거든
Well, no, she's way too emotional.
감정적이란 말은
미쳤다구!
And by emotional, I mean crazy!
내가 중국 음식 시킨 거야
That's just my Chinese food.
여기서 음식까지 시켜 먹어?
She has food delivered here?
감정적인데다 배짱도 좋거든
Yes, she's emotional, but ballsy.
추리닝으로 갈아 입고
이거 침대에서 먹을 거야
I'm gonna get in my sweats
and eat this in bed.
거 봐, 레이첼은 방해가 안 되잖아!
And you thought
she was gonna be in our way!
샴페인이나 열지 그래
금방 올게
Open the champagne,
and I will be right back.
- 자기를 놀래 줄 게 있거든
- 저 방에 또 다른 전처라도 있어?
-I've got a surprise.
-You got another ex-wife back there?
제발 먼저 마시고 있어
Please start drinking.
- 전화만 가져가면 돼요
- 레이첼, 잠깐만요
-I'm just gonna grab the phone.
-Rachel, wait.
기분 나쁘게 생각하지
말았으면 좋겠는데요
I hope you don't take this
the wrong way.
- 여기서 뭐 하는 거예요?
- 전화 필요해요?
-What are you doing?
-Do you need the phone?
아니요
No.
로스가 너무 착해서 말을 못하는데
여긴 로스 아파트예요
Ross is too nice to say it,
but this is his apartment.
우리 선을 분명히 해야겠어요
그러니 집에 가지 그래요
We need boundaries, so why don't
you go back to your place.
근데 모나, 난 여기 사는 걸요
But, Mona, I live here.
해피 발렌타인 데이!
Happy Valentine's Day!
아니면 날 기억할
기념품이 되겠구나
Or, something to remember me by.
- 이번에는 얼마나 오래 간 거야?
- 90초
-How long has it been this time?
-Ninety seconds.
그 생각 안 하고 90초는
긴 시간이야
Ninety seconds is a long time
not to think about it.
사실은 계속 생각하고 있었어
Except all I did was think about it.
알아, 머리에서 떠나질 않아
I know. It haunts me.
이제껏 내가 본 최악은, 아빠가
옷 벗은 일꾼이랑 술 마시는 거였는데
Till now, the worst thing I'd seen was
my dad doing shots off the houseboy.
이젠, 그 장면을 스크린 세이버로
만들어도 상관 없어
After this, I would gladly
make that my screen saver.
우리 이거 극복해야 돼
비디오를 버리고 없었던 일로 하자
We have to get past this.
We'll pretend it never existed.
그러자
I could do that.
이제 의자만 없애면 되겠군
Now all we gotta do
is get rid of this chair.
- 어휴, 다행이다!
- 그러게
-Oh, thank God!
-I know.
들어와!
Come in!
얘들아, 발렌타인 데이에
불쑥 들어와서 미안한데
Hi. I'm sorry to barge in
on your Valentine.
소리지르는 거 피해서 왔어
모나가 로스를 차버리는 중이야
I had to get away from the yelling.
Mona's dumping Ross.
- 세상에
- 불쌍한 로스
-Oh, my God.
-Poor Ross.
속옷 입고 요가 하는 건 보여주면서
이번엔 왜 커튼을 쳐놓은 건데
We watch him do yoga in his underwear,
but for this he closes the drapes.
레이첼, 너 출산비디오
보고 싶어했지?
You know that birthing tape
you wanted to see?
그거 여기 있어
It's here.
너 그거 보기 전에 경고하는데
보지 마
We should warn you before
you watch it. Don't watch it.
봤어? 무서워?
You saw it? Is it scary?
참 이상도 하지
사람이 태어나는 장면이
It's ironic how footage
of someone being born..
오히려 죽고 싶게 만들거든
can make you want to kill yourself.
자기야, 레이첼이 안봐도 될진 몰라도
어차피 겪어야 하는 일이잖아
Honey, she may not have to watch it
but she's going to have to do it.
나 겁 먹었어
너희 나랑 같이 볼 거지?
Now I'm all freaked out.
Will you watch it with me?
아니, 하지만 내 체취가 묻어있는
스웨터를 네 옆에 놓아줄게
No, but I'll leave a sweater that
smells like me right next to you.
모니카, 왜 이래
너도 아이를 갖고 싶다며
Monica, come on.
You want to have kids.
그렇지
I do.
삼신 할머니가 하나
데려다 주겠지 뭐
But the stork
is gonna bring mine.
정말로 너희들 나 혼자
보게 놔두지 않을 거지?
Seriously, you're not gonna
make me watch this alone.
레이첼 말이 맞아
그럴 순 없지
She's right. Of course not.
자기야, 비디오 갖고 와
Honey, get the tape.
이렇게 하니까 그 비디오의
특정 부분이 생각나는 구만
This reminds me of a very specific
part of the tape.
하지만 그 밑에서 닭다리가 나오면
넌 나쁜 룸메이트야
Oh, sure. But if you leave a drumstick
under there and you're a bad roommate.
자, 나온다
Here we go.
어디 보자
Okay.
어머나
Oh, my.
힘내요, 힘내
Come on, come on.
저 애기는 왜 저 여자를
고문하는 거야?
Why is that baby torturing that woman?
나는 이걸 왜 세 번씩이나
봐야 되는 건데?
Why have I seen this thing
three times?
아름답잖아
It's beautiful.
- 끔찍해!
- 맞아! 너 정말 안 됐다, 얘!
-It's horrible!
-I know, I know! I'm so sorry for you!
나 어떡해? 이런 건 하기 싫어!
어떻게 빠져 나갈 방법 없을까?
What do I do? I don't want to do this!
How do I get out of it?
- 너희들, 저것 좀 봐!
- 왜? 저 여자 엉덩이가 터졌어?
-You guys! You guys, look!
-What? Did her ass explode?
아니, 애기가 나왔어, 봐
No, the baby's out. Look.
저 자그마한 손가락
발가락 좀 봐
Look at those little fingers and toes.
그리고 이제 아기 엄마가
얼마나 행복해 하는지도 말야
Look how happy the mom is now.
- 오, 레이첼
- 됐어, 너희는 저런 거 안 해도 되잖아!
-Oh, Rach.
-Screw you! You don't have to do it!
- 어
- 야!
-Hey.
-Hey!
- 무슨 일 있어?
- 모나한테 채였어
-What's up?
-Mona just dumped me.
이런, 안 됐다
왜 그렇게 됐어?
Oh, man, I'm sorry. Why?
요즘 들어 내가 별로 바람직한
남자 친구가 아니었잖아
Lately, I haven't exactly been
the perfect boyfriend.
레이첼 임신시킨 것도
말하지 않았구
I didn't tell her
I got Rachel pregnant.
모나한테 아파트 열쇠 주고선
자물쇠 바꿔버렸구
I gave her a key to my apartment
and then had the locks changed.
레이첼이 이사 온 것에 대해
모나한테 거짓말했구
Then I lied to her about Rachel
moving in with me.
한편으론 모나가 왜 나를 더
빨리 차버리지 않았는지 이상해
In a way, I judge her for not
breaking up with me sooner.
진짜 꽝이구나
그것도 발렌타인 날에
That really sucks.
Especially on Valentine's Day.
가만, 너 여기서 뭐하고 있는거야?
Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
조이가 발렌타인 날
데이트가 없다?
Joey without a date
on Valentine's Day?
어떻게 된 거야? 혹시 여자 문제?
What's going on, huh? Girl trouble?
- 그런 셈이지
- 진짜?
-Sort of.
-Really?
그렇게 좋아할 건 없잖아
You don't have to seem
so happy about it.
내가 도와줄 수
있을지도 모르지
Maybe I can help.
뭔지는 몰라도 분명
나도 한 번 겪었을 거야
Whatever it is,
I am sure it has happened to me.
있잖아, 한 번은
섹스 도중에 채였다구
You know, actually,
once I got dumped during sex.
- 그래, 무슨 일이야?
- 잊어 버려, 별 거 아니야
-So anyway, what is it?
-Forget about it. It's no big deal.
- 말해 봐, 뭔데 그래?
- 아무 것도 아냐
-Come on, what is it?
-It's nothing.
야, 나야, 나
나한테 말 못할 게 뭐냐?
Hey, it's me.
Why can't you tell me?
그래, 좋아, 앉아봐
Okay. Sit down.
내가 많이 좋아하는 여자가 있어
There's this woman that I like a lot.
그런데 그게 복잡해
But it can't happen.
너희 가족은 아니겠지?
She's not a Tribbiani?
아냐!
No!
그럼, 같은 일 하는 여자야?
So is she someone from work?
응
Yes.
그 여자가 너 좋아하니?
Well, does she like you?
가끔 그럴 수도 있다고 생각도 해
Sometimes I think she could.
근데 난 아무 것도 할 수 없어
But I can't do anything about it.
왜 못 해?
Why not?
복잡해
It's complicated.
오랫동안 만나온 남자가 있거든
She was with this other guy
for a long time.
역시 같은 일 하는 사람이구
Someone from work too.
그 남자와는 맞설 수가 없어
우린 친구거든
I could never do that to the guy.
We're friends.
잠깐, 너랑 같이 일하는
사람들 다 싫다면서
Wait, I thought you
hated everyone at work.
그냥 말만 그렇게 하는 거야
No, no. I only say that..
그렇게 해야 챈들러가 겁을 안 내지
그 녀석은 친구가 나 밖에 없으니까
so Chandler won't feel threatened
because I'm his only friend.
뭐라고 하셨수?
Excuse me?
미안, 미안
너도 친구가 나 밖에 없지
Sorry, sorry.
And I'm your only friend too.
그래서, 그 옛날 애인은 아직도
그 여자를 사랑해?
So this guy she used to go out with,
is he still in love with her?
- 그렇지는 않은 것 같아
- 좋아
-No, I don't think so.
-Okay.
괜찮은 남자야?
Is he a good guy?
최고지
Yeah, he's the best.
- 그럼 가서 얘기해
- 모르겠어
-Then talk to him.
-I don't know.
그 여자를 좋아한다면 시도해봐
It's worth finding out,
if you like her.
좋아해, 아주 많이
I do, so much.
그 여자 생각만 해, 잠도 못 자고...
I can't stop thinking about her.
I can't sleep..
그렇다면 더 망설일 이유가 없어
You know what?
You have to go for it.
이런 기회가 자주 올 것 같아?
밀고 나가는 거야
How often does this happen to you?
You owe it to yourself.
여기 따뜻한 우유 나왔수
Here's your warm milk.
집에 가서 버번 위스키나
섞어 마셔야겠다
I'm gonna put the bourbon
in it at home.
어쨌거나, 정말이야
그 남자한테 얘기해, 알았지?
Anyway, seriously,
just talk to the guy, okay?
그리고 어떻게 되었는지
나한테 말해 줘
Let me know how it goes.
레이첼이야
It's Rachel.
아기를 낳을테니 준비를 해야 돼
You're having a baby
and you need to prepare.
비디오를 전부 다 보는거야, 해 봐!
You're gonna make yourself watch
the whole thing. Just do it!
난 스타가 되려고 대도시로 왔어요
I came to the big city
to become a star.
- 스타가 되기 위해선 모든 하겠어요
- 무슨 짓이라도?
-I'll do anything to make that happen.
-Anything?
어떻게 임신하는 지부터
시작되나 보네
Maybe it starts with
how she gets pregnant.
저 남자들 중 누가 아빠가 되는 걸까?
I wonder which one of these guys
becomes the father.
아냐, 아냐
저렇게는 임신 안 되는데
No, no.
Can't get pregnant that way.